(Leonard:)Fine. I'll take him for shoes
next Saturday.
(Penny:)No. A bunch of us from work
are going to Disneyland next Saturday...
(Penny:)...and Sheldon wants to come.
(Leonard:)You're taking him to Disneyland?
(Penny:)Well, he heard me making plans
on the phone. Was I gonna say no?
(Leonard:)All right, but let me know if you're
gonna stuff him with junk food.
I don't wanna bring home a nice dinner
for him and see it go to waste.
(Penny:)We're going to Disneyland.
He's gonna eat junk food.
(Leonard:)All I'm saying is give me a heads-up.
(Penny:)Okay, whatever.
(Leonard:)And don't let him go on Space Mountain
after he eats.
He'll say he can handle it, but you'll
end up with churro puke on your shoes.
All right. Got it. Anything else?
(Leonard:)Don't let Goofy near him.
(Leonard:)He'll have nightmares,
and I'll have to deal with it.
(Penny:)-What's the problem with Goofy?
-Wish I knew. He's fine with Pluto.